BMW X3 F25 (2011-2017) 12.3" HD Navigation & Infotainment System (AutoTecPro)




Hi 

Thank you very much for your inquiry. How are you doing? I hope you are doing well. We do offer this amazing 12.3" High-Definition Touch Screen infotainment system for BMW X3(2011 - 2017) | F25. The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

To verify your vehicle's model, please check the details here before placing your order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/how-to-identify-the-idrive-version-of-the-oem-bmw-system/

This is our newest version which loaded with the newest Android 13. This system retains the original BMW system, you will not lose any of the original features. After the installation, you can also switch between the original BMW system and the new system anytime. It is also fully compatible with the original steering wheel control and original i-Drive as well. If prefer, we also carry the backup camera for this system as well. If your car already come with backup camera, this system will support the original camera and it's not necessary to purchase a separate camera. 

This navigation system comes with 12.3" High-Definition (1920*720 HD LG IPS) Anti-Glare (Blue Anti Reflection Coating) Touch Screen. This system also equipped with the newest generation of Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core Chipsets which will also supports 4G LTE. Compare with the older MTK chipsets, the performance will be boosted by around 40% and hence the system will run much more smoother. It also comes with 4GB DDR4 and 64GB storage memory as well. This system also comes with Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). Our premium version also comes with built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto as well. We will also update the system to the newest version of software as well, such as Google Map, YouTube, Spotify....etc. This android system also fully compatible with the iPhone as well. Our premium version also comes with built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto as well, there is no need to purchase extra CarPlay adapter.

We do also have a demo video to show you how it works, you can also come over to our store and take a look of the system personally as well. 
_________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link (BMW X3 12.3" | F25): https://youtu.be/NtF8PhIzw4w

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
__________________________________________________________________________________
This system can also be purchased from our website:

BMW X3 F25: 2011-2017: https://autotecpro.com/product/bmw-x3-2011-2016-f25-oem-fit-10-25%e2%80%b3-12-3-hd-touch-screen-android-navigation-system-gps-bt-wifi-camera-carplay/
__________________________________________________________________________________

This Android navigation system comes with 12.3" huge HD Touch Screen, Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). We will also update the system to the newest version of software as well, such as Google Map, YouTube, Spotify....etc. This android system also fully compatible with the iPhone as well. it will support the Apple Car Play and Android Auto as well. This system also loads with the newest BMW software ID7 as well.

Furthermore, this system is fully integrated into and compatible with the original system. After the installation, you can still use the original BMW I-Drive to control the new system and operate the new interface. At the same time, you can also access between the original software interface and the new BMW android interface as well. All of the original features are maintained the same as before. 

The premium model comes with the newest Android software interface (UI) and newest map for US and Canada. It also supports the original steering wheel control and stock sound system as well. Other than that, this navigation system comes with GPS (US & Canada), Bluetooth (Phone Call, Phone Book, Music), USB Media Supported, IPOD Ready, Steering Wheel Control, Wifi Internet Connection......etc. During the promotion period, we do also offer the licence of life-time update of the map for free. Here is the price breakdown for this Navigation system: I have also attached some pictures of the premium model in the email just for your reference. 

1) Premium BMW HD Infotainment System (We do have two different options for the hardware for you to choose): 

    Option 1  (12.3"): CAD $ 749 / USD $ 650 (Android 13 | 6GB+128GB | 8-Core CPU | 1920x720 Resolution | 4G LTE | Built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto)

Note: We do also carry more options as well, please refer to our website above for more information.

2) Installation GPS (Included Licence of Life time Update): CAD $100

3) BMW OEM-Fit Wide-Angle HD CCD Camera (With Installation): (Standard Camera Ver.): CAD $ 100 / (BMW OEM HD Ver.): CAD $ 150

4) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 25 (Within Canada) | USD $ 28 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!



