Ford Mustang (2015-2022) 14.4" QHD Tesla Style Navigation & Infotainment System (AutoTecPro)


Hi 

Thank you very much for your inquiry. How are you doing? I hope you are doing well. We do offer this amazing 14.4" QHD 2K (2560 x 1440) Tesla-style navigation system for Ford Mustang (2015-2022). The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Everything needed for installation is included in the package, no additional parts are required. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

To verify your vehicle's model, please check the details here before placing your order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/how-to-identify-different-sync-version-and-ac-climate-control-for-ford-mustang-2015-2021/

This system features the latest Android 13 operating system and is fully compatible with both Apple iPhone and Android Auto. It includes built-in wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto. Equipped with the latest Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core chipsets, it supports 4G LTE and WiFi Hotspot simultaneously. The model comes with a 10.4" or 14.4" QHD IPS touch screen and is fully compatible with the original Microsoft SYNC system. All original features are retained, including the massage seats, heated and cooled steering wheel controls, SONY/B&O premium sound system, steering wheel controls, backup camera, and 360 camera. You can seamlessly switch between the original SYNC interface and the new Android 13 interface at any time.

At your convenience, we would like to confirm which version of Microsoft SYNC is installed in your vehicle. Additionally, we need to verify whether your car has Automatic or Manual AC control. You’re welcome to visit our store for assistance, or alternatively, you can send us a picture of your dashboard, and we’ll confirm the details for you. We’ve also attached a reference photo to help you identify your model more easily.

Note: For this model, we do carry 2 different versions. One is 10.4" and another one is 14.4". Both versions come with Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto. For the premium 14.4" versions, it comes with QHD 2K 2560*1440 IPS Touch Screen, 8GB + 128, QHD 2K TOUCH screen, 4G LTE, Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Core Chipsets. While the standard version of 10.4" comes with 1024*720 touch screen, 6-Core Chipsets, 4GB + 64GB, WiFi. For more details, please refer to our website for more information. The difference between both version shown as below:
________________________________________________________________________________________________________

For 14.4" 2K QHD Version:
Screen: 14.4" 2K QHD (2560 x 1440) Touch Screen
Android Version: Android 13
Processor: Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores Center Processors
Memory: 8 GB RAM + 128 GB Storage
Connectivity: WiFi, GPS, 4G LTE
Wireless CarPlay & Android Auto: Yes
Retain Original SYNC System (SYNC 2 & 3): Yes
DSP: Yes

________________________________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link 14.4" QHD Version (FORD Mustang | 2015-2023): 

1) Demo Video 1: https://youtu.be/6CBeNCv1qvw?si=HkLQjmqnHicFCJ7X

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
This system (14.4" Version) can also be purchased from our website:

Ford Mustang | 2015-2021 (14.4" QHD Version): https://autotecpro.com/product/ford-mustang-2015-2022-14-4-ips-qhd-2k-touch-screen-android-navigation-system-android-11-gps-bt-wifi-carplay-android-auto-4g-lte/
________________________________________________________________________________________________________

Both models comes with wireless Apple CarPlay & Android Auto, 4G LTE, Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, Offline GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). It will also retain the original Sirius XM radio and Microsoft Syn as well. Also, it retains the original physical climate control buttons on the original system. It also supports the original steering wheel control and stock sound system as well. Other than that, this navigation system comes with worldwide GPS, Bluetooth (Phone Call, Phone Book, Music), USB Media Supported, IPOD Ready, Steering Wheel Control, Wifi Internet Connection......etc. Here is the price breakdown for this Navigation system: I have also attached some pictures of the premium model in the email just for your reference. 


1) Premium Android Tesla Style Ver. GPS system (We do have two different options for the hardware for you to choose):

    14.4" Tesla Version: CAD $ 1299 / USD $ 1050 (Android 13 | 14.4" 2560*1440 | 8GB + 128GB | Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores CPU | Wireless Apple CarPlay & Android Auto

2) Installation (If applicable): CAD $ 250

3) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 30 (Within Canada) | USD $ 35 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!


