Range Rover Sport / Vogue / Evoque (2013-2018) 12.3"/13.3" HD Navigation & Infotainment System (AutoTecPro)




Hi 

Thank you very much for your inquiry. How are you doing? I hope you are doing well. We do offer this premium High-Definition Touch Screen infotainment system for the Range Rover Sport / Vogue / Evoque (2013–2018), available in two different sizes: 12.3" and 13.3". Designed to elevate your driving experience, it features advanced technology with seamless integration. This system fully retains your original car functions, including the Car Info System, 360° camera, and both the Meridian and Bose Premium Sound Systems. After installation, you can easily switch between the factory system and the new infotainment system at any time. The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

In order to confirm the model of your vehicle, please have a look here before order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/land-rover-compatibility/

This system comes with the newest version of Android 13 operating system, while it is also fully compatible with both Apple iPhone and Android Auto. It comes with built-in wireless Apple CarPlay and wireless Android Auto. It also equipped with the newest generation of Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core chipsets, it supports both 4G LTE, WiFi Hotspot at the same time. This model comes with the 12.3" / 13.3" HD IPS Touch Screen. It is also fully compatible with the original Meridian / Bose premium sound system. All the original features will be retained, included original massage seat, original heated and cooled steering wheel control, original Meridian / Bose premium sound system, original steering wheel, original backup camera, original 360 camera...etc. It also retain all other original features, such as the tow haul, exhaust, trailer brake...etc since the original control panel will be retained completely on the new system as well.

If you are not confirmed which model will fit to your vehicle, please refer to the link above, it will help you to identify the model of your vehicle. You can also send us a picture with the original screen turned on, we will be able to confirm for you as well. 

This system comes with 12.3" / 13.3" High-Definition (1920*720 HD LG IPS) Anti-Glare HD Touch Screen. This system also equipped with the newest generation of Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core Chipsets which will also supports 4G LTE. Compare with the older MTK chipsets, the performance will be boosted by around 40% and hence the system will run much more smoother. It also comes with 8 GB DDR4 and 128 GB storage memory as well. This system also comes with Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). Our premium version also comes with built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto as well. We will also update the system to the newest version of software as well, such as Google Map, YouTube, Spotify....etc. This android system also fully compatible with the iPhone as well. Our premium version also comes with built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto as well, there is no need to purchase extra CarPlay adapter.

__________________________________________________________________________________
For 12.3" Version:
Screen: 12.3" HD Touch Screen
Android Version: Android 13
Processor: Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores Center Processors
Memory: 8 GB RAM + 128 GB Storage
Connectivity: WiFi, GPS
Wireless CarPlay & Android Auto: Yes
Retain Original Heated and Ventilated Seats: Yes
DSP: Yes
Color Available: Black / Pimento Red / Ivory White / Vintage Tan / Almond

For 13.3" Version:
Screen: 13.3" HD Touch Screen
Android Version: Android 13
Processor: Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores Center Processors
Memory: 8 GB RAM + 128 GB Storage
Connectivity: WiFi, GPS, 4G LTE
Wireless CarPlay & Android Auto: Yes
Retain Original Heated and Ventilated Seats: Yes
DSP: Yes
Color Available: Black
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link 13.3" Version : 

1) Demo Video 1: https://youtu.be/vg2Y-XU6RIU

Product Demo Video for Digital A/C climate control Panel: https://youtu.be/H0A7rAwBPMM

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
__________________________________________________________________________________
This system (12.3" Version) can also be purchased from our website:

Range Rover Sport (2013 - 2018): https://autotecpro.com/product/land-rover-range-rover-sport-2014-2017-12-3%e2%80%b3-hd-ips-touch-screen-navigation-infotainment-system-android-13-gps-bt-wifi-carplay-bosch-harman-4g-lte/

Range Rover Vogue (2013 - 2018): https://autotecpro.com/product/land-rover-range-rover-vogue-2013-2017-12-3%e2%80%b3-hd-ips-touch-screen-navigation-infotainment-system-android-13-gps-bt-wifi-carplay-bosch-harman-4g-lte/

__________________________________________________________________________________
This system (13.3" Version) can also be purchased from our website:

Range Rover Sport / Vogue / Evoque (2013 - 2018): https://autotecpro.com/product/land-rover-range-rover-vogue-sport-evoque-2013-2017-13-3-hd-ips-touch-screen-navigation-infotainment-systemid-13-gps-bt-wifi-carplay-bosch-harman-4g-lte/
__________________________________________________________________________________

The premium model includes the latest Android software interface (UI) and updated maps for the U.S. and Canada. It supports the original steering wheel controls and the factory sound system. In addition, the navigation system offers world wide GPS, Bluetooth for calls, phone book access, and music, USB media support, iPod readiness, steering wheel control integration, and Wi-Fi internet connectivity, among other features. During our promotional period, we are also offering a lifetime map update license at no extra cost. Below is the price breakdown for this navigation system. I’ve attached some pictures of the premium model in this email for your reference.


1) Premium Range Rover HD Infotainment System (We do have two different options for the hardware for you to choose): 

    Option 1 (12.3"): CAD $ 1,249 / USD $ 1,010 (Android 13 | 8GB+128GB | 8-Core CPU | 1920x720 Resolution | 4G LTE | Built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto)

    Option 2 (13.3"): CAD $ 1,149 / USD $ 930 (Android 13 | 8GB+128GB | 8-Core CPU | 1920x720 Resolution | 4G LTE | Built-in Wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto)

Note: We do also carry more options as well, please refer to our website above for more information.

2) Installation GPS (Included Licence of Life time Update): CAD $ 250

3) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 25 (Within Canada) | USD $ 28 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!





