Hi 

Thanks very much for your inquiry. We do carry the ANDROID OEM fit navigation system for the Lexus CT200H. This Android navigation system comes with 10.25" huge HD Touch Screen, Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). We will also update the system to the newest version of software as well, such as Google Map, YouTube, Spotify....etc. This android system also fully compatible with the iPhone as well. it will support the Apple Car Play and Android Auto as well.
__________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link (1): https://youtu.be/V2HEdfrD2yc

Product Demo Video Link (2): https://youtu.be/mfxaQEpIrHI
__________________________________________________________________________________
This system can also be purchased from our website:

Lexus CT200h Series | 2011-2018 | 10.25" HD: https://autotecpro.com/product/lexus-ct200h-2011-2018-oem-fit-10-25%e2%80%b3-hd-touch-screen-android-navigation-system-gps-bt-wifi-a2dp-camera/
__________________________________________________________________________________

Furthermore, this system is fully integrated into and compatible with the original system. After the installation, you can still use the original controller to control the new system and operate the new interface. At the same time, you can also access between the original software interface and the new Lexus android interface as well. All of the original features are maintained the same as before. 

The premium model comes with the newest Android software interface (UI) and newest map for US and Canada. It also supports the original steering wheel control and stock sound system as well. Other than that, this navigation system comes with GPS (US & Canada), Bluetooth (Phone Call, Phone Book, Music), USB Media Supported, IPOD Ready, Steering Wheel Control, Wifi Internet Connection......etc. During the promotion period, we do also offer the licence of life-time update of the map for free. Here is the price breakdown for this Navigation system: I have also attached some pictures of the premium model in the email just for your reference. 

1) Premium Lexus 10.25" HD Android Ver. GPS system (Lexus CT200H): CAD $ 1099 / USD $ 850

2) Installation GPS (Included Licence of Life time Update): CAD $ 100

3) Lexus HD OEM-Fit Wide-Angle CCD Camera (With Installation): CAD $ 150

4) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 30 (Within Canada) | USD $ 35 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at (647) 962-3113 or (416) 291-2868. We will be more than happy to assist you. We are located on "CarTec, Unit 14, 4732 Sheppard Ave. East, Scarborough, ON, M1S 3V6 (McCowen and Sheppard/ Hwy 401)". Our office hour is Monday to Saturday (10:00am - 7:00pm), Sunday will be by appointment. Thanks very much again and have a nice day.




