Ford Fusion (2013 - 2020) 13.6" HD Tesla Style Navigation & Infotainment System (AutoTecPro)




Hi 

Thank you for your inquiry. How are you doing? I hope you are doing well. Yes, we do offer the Tesla-style Android infotainment system for Ford Fusion (2013-2020). The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Everything needed for installation is included in the package, no additional parts are required. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

In order to confirm the model of your vehicle, please have a look here before order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/how-to-identify-different-microsoft-sync-version-and-ac-climate-control-for-ford-fusion-2013-2020/

We do carry this fantastic 13.6" Android 13 OEM-Fit Tesla style navigation system for the Ford Fusion (2013-2020). This system is fully compatible with the original features, included but not limited to: Steering Wheel Control, Original backup camera, Original Microsoft SYNC....etc

This system runs on the latest Android 13 OS and is fully compatible with both Apple iPhone and Android Auto. It includes built-in wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto, and is powered by the latest Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core chipset, supporting 4G LTE and WiFi Hotspot simultaneously. Available in 12.1" or 14.4" HD IPS touchscreens, it also retains compatibility with Microsoft SYNC 2 (if applicable to your vehicle), ensuring all original features like the premium SONY sound system, steering wheel controls, backup camera, 360 camera, and Sirius XM radio (with SYNC 2) are preserved. You can easily switch between the original SYNC 2 interface and the Android 13 interface at any time.

Since this model will be fully compatible with the original Microsoft SYNC and Original Climate Control, we would like to confirm which Microsoft SYNC version comes with your vehicle. Also, we would like to confirm if your car comes with Automatic AC control or Manual AC control as well. If possible, you can come over to our store and we can confirm that for you. Or you can take a picture of your dash and send it to us and we can also confirm these details for you as well. We have attached a document for you so it may be easier for you to check it out on your vehicle. 

________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link (Ford Fusion | 2013-2020): https://youtu.be/2MIbFGute7k

*This video was taken from a Ford Explorer, however, the Ford Fusion tesla system will work the same way as Ford Explorer model. It's for a reference. 

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
__________________________________________________________________________________
This system can also be purchased from our website:

Ford Fusion (2013-2020) 13.6" HD PX6 Tesla Screen: https://autotecpro.com/product/ford-fusion-2013-2020-13-6%e2%80%b3-ips-hd-touch-screen-android-navigation-system-gps-bt-wifi-sync-wireless-carplay-android-auto/
__________________________________________________________________________________
This premium model feature with wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto, 4G LTE, WiFi Hotspot connectivity, Google Maps, Bluetooth, and offline GPS (which can acquire a GPS signal without a data connection). This infotainment system offers world wide GPS coverage, Bluetooth, USB media support, iPod compatibility, and WiFi internet access. 


The premium model comes with the newest Android software interface (UI) and newest map for US and Canada. It also supports the original steering wheel control and stock sound system as well. Other than that, this navigation system comes with GPS (US & Canada), Bluetooth (Phone Call, Phone Book, Music), USB Media Supported, IPOD Ready, Steering Wheel Control, Wifi Internet Connection......etc. During the promotion period, we do also offer the license of life-time update of the map for free. Here is the price breakdown for this Navigation system: I have also attached some pictures of the premium model in the email just for your reference. 

1) Premium Android Tesla Style Ver. GPS system (We do have two different options for the hardware for you to choose):

   13.6" HD Tesla Version: CAD $ 1029 / USD $ 798 (Android 13 | 13.8" HD | Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores CPU | Wireless Apple CarPlay & Android Auto)

2) Installation (If applicable): CAD $ 200

3) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 30 (Within Canada) | USD $ 35 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!
