Ford Expedition (2018-2021) 14.4" QHD 2K Navigation & infotainment System (AutoTecPro)





Hi 

Thank you very much for your inquiry. How are you doing? I hope you are doing well. We do offer this amazing 14.4" QHD 2K (2560 x 1440) Tesla-style navigation system for Ford Expedition (2018-2021). It is designed to enhance your driving experience with advanced technology and seamless integration. This system retains the original SYNC system, including all original features like the 360 camera, Original SYNC, B&O premium sound system, Ford Pass app...etc. The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

To confirm the model of your vehicle, please check here before placing your order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/how-to-confirm-the-compatibility-for-ford-expedition-2018-2021/

This system It features a stunning 14.4" QHD 2K (2560*1440) IPS touchscreen, 8GB of RAM, and 128GB of storage. It also runs on the latest Android 13 operating system and is fully compatible with both Apple iPhone and Android Auto. It comes with built-in wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto for a seamless experience. Powered by the latest Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core processors, therefore it supports simultaneous 4G LTE and WiFi Hotspot connectivity. It integrates perfectly with the original Microsoft SYNC system, retaining all original features such as massage seats, SONY / B&O Premium Sound System, heated and cooled seat, steering wheel controls, steering wheel controls, backup camera, and 360 camera. You can also easily switch between the original SYNC interface and the new Android 13 interface at any time.
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
14.4" 2K QHD Version:
Screen: 14.4" 2K QHD (2560 x 1440) Touch Screen
Android Version: Android 13
Processor: Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores Center Processors
Memory: 8 GB RAM + 128 GB Storage
Connectivity: WiFi, GPS, 4G LTE
Wireless CarPlay & Android Auto: Yes
Retain Original SYNC System (SYNC 2 & 3): Yes
DSP: Yes
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
1) Product Demonstration Video : https://youtu.be/-FMdeYiwHVk

2) Product Demonstration Video : https://youtu.be/gqGsc4K2iqw

3) Product Demonstration Video : https://youtu.be/JtK5_3xbAZc

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
This system (14.4" Version) can also be purchased from our website:

Ford Expedition | 2018 - 2021 (14.4" QHD): https://autotecpro.com/product/ford-expedition-2018-2021-14-4-ips-qhd-2k-touch-screen-navigation-infotainment-system-android-11-gps-bt-wifi-carplay-sync-4g-lte/
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
This system also features wireless Apple CarPlay and Android Auto, 4G LTE, WiFi hotspot internet connectivity, Google Maps, Bluetooth, and offline GPS that works without a data connection. It retains the original Sirius XM radio, Microsoft SYNC, and physical climate control buttons. Additionally, it fully supports factory steering wheel controls and the original sound system. Below is the price breakdown for this navigation system. I've also attached pictures of the premium model in the email for your reference.

1) Premium Android Tesla Style Ver. GPS system (We do have two different options for the hardware for you to choose):

    14.4" Tesla Version: CAD $ 1299 / USD $ 1050 (Android 13 | 14.4" 2560*1440 | 8GB + 128GB | Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores CPU | Wireless Apple CarPlay & Android Auto

2) Installation (If applicable): CAD $ 200

3) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 30 (Within Canada) | USD $ 35 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!


