Ford Explorer (2011-2020) 14.4" QHD Tesla Style Navigation & Infotainment System (AutoTecPro)



Hi 

How are you doing today? Thanks very much for your inquiry. We do carry this fantastic ANDROID OEM-Fit Tesla style navigation system for the Ford Explorer (2011-2020). The system comes with screen and bezel, it's one piece. The system is completely plug-and-play, requiring no modifications or wire cutting. Additionally, we provide a full video tutorial for installation. Our technical support center is located in Toronto, it also ensures seamless communication for all your technical inquiries.

To confirm the model of your vehicle, please check here before placing your order:

>> https://autotecpro.com/how-to-distinguish-microsoft-sync-version-and-ac-model-on-ford-explorer/

This system comes with the newest version of Android 13 operating system and a 14.4" QHD 2K TOUCH screen while it is also fully compatible with both Apple iPhone and Android Auto. This system is also fully compatible with all the original features, included but not limited to: Steering Wheel Control, Original backup camera, Original Microsoft SYNC, Original Climate Control....etc

Since this model will be fully compatible with the original Microsoft SYNC (SYNC 2 and SYNC 3) and Original Climate Control, we would like to confirm which Microsoft SYNC version comes with your vehicle. Also, we would like to confirm if your car comes with Automatic AC control or Manual AC control as well. If possible, you can come over to our store and we can confirm that for you. Or you can take a picture of your dash and send it to us and we can also confirm these details for you as well. We have attached a document for you so it may be easier for you to check it out on your vehicle. 

Not: For the premium 14.4" versions, it comes with QHD 2K 2560*1440 IPS Touch Screen, 8GB+128, QHD 2K TOUCH screen, 4G LTE, Qualcomm Snapdragon Octa-Core Chipset. 
________________________________________________________________________________________________________
For 14.4" 2K QHD Version:
Screen: 14.4" 2K QHD (2560 x 1440) Touch Screen
Android Version: Android 11
Processor: Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores Center Processors
Memory: 8 GB RAM + 128 GB Storage
Connectivity: WiFi, GPS, 4G LTE
Wireless CarPlay & Android Auto: Yes
Retain Original SYNC System (SYNC 2 & 3): Yes
DSP: Yes
________________________________________________________________________________
Product Demo Video Link (FORD Explorer | 2011-2020): https://youtu.be/k2wh88Lxnis

(Note: If you find that our video is informative, please don't forget to subscribe our channel so we can keep an update of the information for you. Thanks very much and have a nice day.)
__________________________________________________________________________________
This system can also be purchased from our website:

Ford Explorer (2011-2020) 14.4" QHD 2K Tesla Screen: https://autotecpro.com/product/ford-explorer-2011-2019-13-6-hd-touch-screen-android-navigation-system/
__________________________________________________________________________________

This version comes with 8GB + 128GB. More memory will ensure the system runs smoother and faster as well. The system comes with builtin Apple Carplay, Steering Wheel control, original USB and 36 Camera as well. It also comes Wifi Hotspot Internet connection, Google Map, Bluetooth, GPS (Can acquire GPS signal without data connection...etc). The premium version will retain the original Sirius XM radio and Microsoft Syn as well. Also, it also retain the original climate control, original USB, camera..etc. This newest model also comes with the newest Android 11 and newest map for US and Canada. It also supports the original steering wheel control and stock sound system as well. Other than that, this navigation system comes with GPS (US & Canada), Bluetooth (Phone Call, Phone Book, Music), USB Media Supported, IPOD Ready, Steering Wheel Control, Wifi Internet Connection......etc. During the promotion period, we do also offer the licence of life-time update of the map for free. Here is the price breakdown for this Navigation system: I have also attached some pictures of the premium model in the email just for your reference. 


1) Premium Android Tesla Style Ver. GPS system:

    14.4" Tesla Version: CAD $ 1238 / USD $ 988 (Android 11 | 14.4" 2560*1440 2K | 8GB + 128GB | Qualcomm Snapdragon 8-Cores CPU | Wireless Apple CarPlay & Android Auto)

2) Installation (If applicable): CAD $ 200

3) Express Shipping Service is also available: CAD $ 30 (Within Canada) | USD $ 35 (United States) | For all international Shipping: Please enter your address on the checkout page and our system will be able to calculate it for you automatically. 

(Note: If you decide to install it by yourself, we can also provide you with detail installation video and show you step by step as well. )

If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at +1 (905) 477-5888 or +1 (905) 477-5889. We will be more than happy to assist you. Our office is located at AutoTecPro, 7725 Birchmount Rd, Unit #22, Markham, ON, L3R 9X3 (at the intersection of 14th Ave and Birchmount Rd.). Our office hours are Monday to Saturday from 10:00 AM to 7:00 PM, and we are available by appointment on Sunday. Thank you again, and have a great day!



